# Linus Peng

1012/601 Little Lonsdale Street • Melbourne • VIC 3000

Phone (61) 0426-829324 • E-MAIL penxumelb@gmail.com • Website: https://linusmelb.github.io

### **EDUCATION** The University of Melbourne

Bachelor of Science, Software Systems

National University of Singapore – 2017.07 - 2017.12

The exchange program, Computer Science

#### **SUMMARY**

Innovative tech mind with 3 years of experience working as a web developer. Capable of working with a variety of technology and software solutions, and managing databases. A valuable team member who has experience diagnosing problems and developing solutions. Talented programmer with unique ideas and a huge passion for learning new things.

#### **SKILLS**

**Analytics Service:** GA, GTM, Firebase analytics (App tracking)

Database: BigQuery, MSSQL, Mysql

Cloud Platform: GCP, Azure, Digitalocean

**Deployment Tools:** Jenkins

**Proxy Server:** Nginx

RCS: Git

Others: Kubernetes, Webpack, Tableau, Vuejs

**EXPERIENCE** 

### Webjet Limited (ASX: WEB), Analytics Developer

#### 2018.11 - Present

- Enhancing data collection procedures to include information that is relevant for building analytic systems
- Building a system for processing, cleansing, and verifying the integrity of data used for analysis.
- Implementing firebase tracking on Webjet's iOS and Android apps
- Managing and improving GTM tags to quickly and easily update measurement codes and related code fragments.
- Building an analytics website (Vue.js, Flask, and Kubernetes) to manage all jobs in the scheduling system

**Novatti Group Limited(ASX: NOV),** Software developer & SEO developer 2018.07 – 2018.10

- Project link <a href="https://www.chinapayments.com">https://www.chinapayments.com</a>
- Led, architected and participated in the design, testing, and deployment of client/server
- Designed a brand new UI for the site and Integrated Bootstrap4 and ParticleJs into the site
- Handled problems/issues and make prompt solutions to resolve them
- Helped boost the company's online presence & website traffic

# **Radio Fodder - University of Melbourne Student Radio,** Web developer 2018.01 – 2018.08

- Project link http://www.radiofodder.com
- Redesigned and developed the site individually
- Integrated a new online radio system into the site

# Chinese Students and Scholars Association (CSSA), Head of IT department 2016.09 – 2017.09

- Project link <a href="http://www.cssaunimelb.com">http://www.cssaunimelb.com</a>
- Designed a brand new website for CSSA
- Developed a membership management system to store more than 5000+ members' information
- Manage and support critical online information systems of CSSA

### **MelMel Consulting PTY LTD,** Software Developer 2015.06 – 2017.01

- Project link:
  - o http://www.reioiceworld.com.au
  - o <a href="http://www.melmel.com.au/service">http://www.melmel.com.au/service</a>
  - Revised programming and software development projects by updating code and working to improve functionality.
  - Designed and deployed the WordPress website for customers

OTHER PROJECTS	Subject rating platform(6.6k users): <a href="https://uzhan.com.au">https://uzhan.com.au</a> Second-hand marketplace(2.3k users): <a href="https://xdd.com.au">https://xdd.com.au</a>
LANGUAGE	English – Fluent Mandarin – Native